A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers, Financial Material, Vouchers, Subseries FV FA262
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial Material, 1893-1916; F; 184.73 Cubic Feet
  - Vouchers - L, FV 7
    - L32581 - L32760, 1910 January 26-February 10 (Box 51)
    - L32761 - L32960, 1910 February 11-March 28 (Box 52)
    - L32961 - L33220, 1910 March 28-May 2 (Box 53)
    - L33221 - L33410, 1910 May 2-June 6 (Box 54)
    - L33411 - L33590, 1910 June 6-28 (Box 55)
    - L33591 - L33790, 1910 June 28-July 22 (Box 56)
    - L33791 - L34000, 1910 July 22-August 26 (Box 57)
    - L34001 - L34210, 1910 August 26-October 31 (Box 58)
    - L34211 - L34390, 1910 October 31-November 28 (Box 59)
    - L34391 - L34600, 1910 November 28-December 19 (Box 60)
    - L34601 - L34850, 1910 December 19-1911 March 3 (Box 61)
    - L34851 - L35070, 1911 March 3-April 4 (Box 62)
    - L35071 - L35300, 1911 April 4-28 (Box 63)
    - L35301 - L35520, 1911 April 28-June 15 (Box 64)
    - L35521 - L35760, 1911 June 15-July 27 (Box 65)
    - L35761 - L36040, 1911 July 27-August 18 (Box 66)
    - L36041 - L36320, 1911 August 18-September 21 (Box 67)
    - L36321 - L36540, 1911 September 21-October 23 (Box 68)
    - L36541 - L36750, 1911 October 23-December 4 (Box 69)
    - L36751 - L37000, 1911 December 4-1912 January 16 (Box 70)
    - L37001 - L37300, 1912 January 16-April 4 (Box 71)
    - L37301 - L37340, L37541 - L37580, 1912 April 4-May 31 (Box 72)
    - L37581 - L37860, 1912 May 31-July 18 (Box 73)
    - L37861 - L38150, 1912 July 19-October 8 (Box 74)
    - L38151 - L38430, 1912 October 2-December 6 (Box 75)
    - L38431 - L38660, 1912 December 6-1913 January 6 (Box 76)
    - L38661 - L38920, 1913 January 6-February 25 (Box 77)
    - L38921 - L39200, 1913 February 25-May 1 (Box 78)
    - L39201 - L39440, 1913 May 1-June 12 (Box 79)
    - L39441 - L39680, 1913 June 12-September 3 (Box 80)
    - L39681 - L39920, 1913 September 3-November 28 (Box 81)
    - L39921 - L40220, 1913 November 19-1914 June 15 (Box 82)
    - L40221 - L40460, 1914 June 15-October 15 (Box 83)
    - L40461 - L40567, 1914 October 15-December 31 (Box 84)
    - L1569 - L1842, 1906 December 31-1907 April 23 (Box 85)
  - Vouchers - FH, FV 8
    - FH1 - FH200, 1914 December 31-1915 June 15 (Box 1)
    - FH201 - FH400, 1915 June 15-September 13 (Box 2)
    - FH401 - FH500, 1915 September 25-1916 January 19 (Box 3)
  - Sales and Rents, FV 9
    - 42240 - 45390, 1910 January 4-1915 December 10 (Box 1)
  - Vouchers - O, FV 10
    - O1 - O200, 1915 January 1-1915 February 20 (Box 1)
    - O201 - O398, 1915 February 25-April 30 (Box 2)
    - O401 - O600, 1915 May 1-July 10 (Box 3)
    - O601 - O800, 1915 July 8-October 6 (Box 4)
    - O801 - O1200, 1915 August 31-December 24 (Box 5)
    - O1201 - O1400, 1915 December 31-1916 March 13 (Box 6)
    - O4101 - O1509, 1916 March 13-April 25 (Box 7)
  - Ledgers, FV 11
    - 1 - 210, 1915 January 21-June 21 (Box 1)
    - 211 - 420, 1915 June 22-December 23 (Box 2)
    - 421 - 530, 1915 December 24-1916 March 20 (Box 3)
    - 531 - 698, 1916 March 16-July 31 (Box 4)
  - Vouchers - M, FV 12
    - M12451 - M12650, 1893 May 29-June 29 (Box 1)
    - M12651 - M12900, 1893 June 29-August 11 (Box 2)
    - M12901 - M13130, 1893 August 11-September 28 (Box 3)
    - M13131 - M13370, 1893 September 28-November 3 (Box 4)
    - M13371 - M13610, 1893 November 3-December 4 (Box 5)
    - M13611 - M13860, 1893 December 4-30 (Box 6)
    - M13861 - M14100, 1893 December 30-1894 January 23 (Box 7)
    - M14101 - M14340, 1894 January 23-February 20 (Box 8)
    - M14341 - M14580, 1894 February 21-April 30 (Box 9)
    - M14581 - M14800, 1894 April 30-July 3 (Box 10)
    - M14801 - M15040, 1894 July 3-September 22 (Box 11)
    - M15040A - M15125, 1894 September 22-October 24 (Box 12)
  - Vouchers - M, FV 13
    - M31295 - M31430, 1909 June 29-July 26 (Box 1)
    - M31431 - M31524, 1909 July 29-August 12 (Box 2)
  - Voucher Indexes, 1887-1916; FV 15
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Donations, 1887, Voucher 1-1463, 1887 January-1888 January; Spine areas along the edges and corners are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Areas of the board are faded and frayed. (Box 101)
      Scope and Contents
      Inside Book Plate - C.S. Nathan, Manufacturer, No. 2777
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Donations, 1888, Voucher 1464-3196, 1888 January-1889 January; Corner areas of board and spine are faded and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 102)
      Inside Book Plate - Standard Oil Co. Stationary Department, Order No. 5896
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Donations, 1889, Voucher 3197-4959, 1889 January-1890 January; Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 103)
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Donations, 1890, Vouchers 4971-7100, 1890 January-1891 January; Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 104)
      Inside Book Plate - Wallace D. Barkley, Manufacturer No. 12429
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Donations, 1891-1892, Vouchers 7108-8760, 1891 January-1892 January; Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages are detached from stiching, crash and spine. (Box 105)
      Inside Book Plate - Wallace D. Barkley, Manufacturer No. 19132
    - Voucher Index, Series Pre-A - Bills, 1891-1892, Vouchers 7101-9272, 1891 January-1892 January; Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 106)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1896, 1896-1897; Damage to spine. Paper secure and intact. (Box 16)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1897, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure with water stains along lower edges. Pages and gutters are intact and secure with water stains along lower edges. (Box 108)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1898-1899, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 109)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1900, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 110)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1900, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 110)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1901, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 111)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1902, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 112)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1903, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 113)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1904, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 114)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1905, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 115)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1906, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn and frayed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 116)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1907, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 117)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22449, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1908, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 118)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22474, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1909, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 119)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22464, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1910, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 120)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 27211, Year 1909
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1911, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 121)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, Printing, No. 77152. The Burr Index Company, Manufacturer, October 1, 1907.
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1912, Areas of the board, and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Areas of the spine are worn, frayed and detached from the foot joint. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 122)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 29177, Year 1911
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1913, Areas of the board are worn and frayed. Spine is worn, frayed and detached from the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 123)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 29785, Year 1912
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1914, Areas of the board are worn and frayed. Spine is worn, frayed and detached from the foot joint. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 124)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 30441
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1915, Areas of the board, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 125)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, Printing, No. B 10061. The Burr Index Company, Manufacturer, 1914
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Donations, 1916, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached from the foot joint. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 126)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1894, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's stiching are loose and splitting apart. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 127)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 4901
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1895, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 128)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1896, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 129)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1897, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 130)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1898, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 131)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15093, Year 1897
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1899, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 132)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15088, Year 1897
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1900, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 133)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15129, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1901, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 134)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15110, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1902, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 135)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15122, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1903, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 136)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15100, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1904, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 137)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22467, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1905, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 138)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22451, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1906, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 139)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1907 (Box 140)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1908, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn with joints exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's bindings and stitching are loose and separating along the gutter. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 141)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 25928, Year 1907
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1909, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn with joints exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's bindings and stitching are loose and separating along the gutter. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 142)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 26464, Year 1908
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1910, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 143)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 27213, Year 1909
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1911, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 144)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, No. A 77153. The Burr Index Company, 1911
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1912, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 145)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, No. A 86168. The Burr Index Company, 1911
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1913, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 146)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, No. A 95067. The Burr Index Company, No. 29786, Year 1912
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1914, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is worn, detached in front, and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 147)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, No. B 2171. The Burr Index Company, Year 1913
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Bills, 1915, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached and cracked along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 148)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and BRO, No. B 10060. The Burr Index Company, Year 1914
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 15001-17000, 1902 January 30-November 10; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 149)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 4695
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 17001-19000, 1902 November 10-1903 July 7; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 150)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 5998
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 19001-21000, 1903 July 7-1904 March 17; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 151)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 6953
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 21001-23000, 1904 March 17-November 15; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 152)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 7759
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 23001-25000, 1904 November 15-1905 June 15; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 153)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 8508
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 25001-27000, 1905 June 15-1906 January 10; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 154)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 9803
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 27001-29000, 1906 January 11-July 31; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 155)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 29001-31000, 1906 July 31-1907 February 13; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 156)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 31001-33000, 1907 February 13-August 19; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 157)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 33001-35000, 1907 August 19-1908 March 9; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 158)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 35001-37000, 1908 March 10-September 21; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 159)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 37001-39000, 1908 September 21-1909 March 12; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 160)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 39001-41000, 1909 March 12-September 27; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 161)